This book...
What is Grandfather's
storybook doing here?
Hello!
What brings you here?
Sorry...
Are you Qi Nona?
Ninya sent me to speak with you.
Ah. So, you're helping her hatch the laputa?
Here. Take the low-grade synthester she left with me,
but first, may I say something strange?
You see, I can't shake this feeling that we've met before.
Really?
Maybe you can tell me about this book then.
I have a copy just like it,
so I was surprised to see it here.
Hmm.
There's this old wives' tale.
It says that, like a coin, there's another world on the opposite side of Iblard.
If the two of us owning the same book is anything to go by,
I wonder if that particular tale is true.
Tell me, friend, what is your world like?
Very hectic! It's the opposite of Iblard.
I see. Then maybe we are two sides of the same coin.
Oh!
I know! Why not take that book with you?
It might come in handy.