Thank goodness those blasted Takatsung airships flew off.
Although, I've no doubt they're plotting a comeback.
Ack! Who are you?!
You're not from this land, are you?
No, you followed us here from that city!
Oh, this won't do!
That rift in space-time has long since closed up!
I traveled through space-time?!
Yes, you followed us to Iblard from your world.
Are we in Iblard right now?
You've heard of Iblard?!
Yes, but I never knew it really existed!
It's just like Grandpa's storybook!
That doesn't make sense.
Your Grandfather came to Iblard and went back home? Impossible!
You say that like there's
no way for me to do the same.
I hate to tell you this,
but that's is what I'm saying.
You're kidding!
Let me think...
To find another rift in space-time,
your only hope is to find a laputa as it hatches.
A laputa...as it hatches?
That's when a new floating island is born, right—
Uh-oh! Just look at the time!
I've other preparations to make!
Hey, wait, you!
When and where does do the laputa hatch?!
"You" is Schopello, thank you!
And you'll have to ask a magician for a better answer to that.
Here. This will get you to the next station.
My friend, Melkinso, lives on a pond down the way.
He'll be happy to help you with your laputa problem.
Good luck!
Darn!