Why hello. How can I assist you?
You're...Ninya, aren't you?
It is.
In a way, we've met before, no?
How did you get to Iblard?
Well, uh...you see...
...and now I'm here.
I see now.
So, if we can hatch a Laputa, you can return to your world.
Actually, did you speak to Burgalad in the forest?
Burgalad? Was he the guy covered in leaves?
Yes, that's Burgalad.
He's the wise man of the forest.
If you speak with him, he has a wealth of knowledge to share.
I couldn't understand his language.
Tee hee!
That would be a roadblock, wouldn't it?
After all, you're not a magician like we are.
May I see your map for a moment?
I'll mark the locations of the ores we need.
Thanks.
I left the low-grade synthester we found in your world
with a young man named Qi Nona.
He too is a magician.
He lives in the Nona family house on a nearby hill.
Okay then.
I'll visit Qi Nona's house next.
I'll give you this too.
That's an airship energy source.
If your airship runs out of energy
keep a look out for energy sources.
Thank you very much.
You and Qi Nona are what I'd call "kindred spirits".
Let's find the ores together.