What's he doing by himself?
Tending to those flowers, like always.
Why don't we invite him to hang out?
I don't see that working.
He already turned us down before.
"Sorry, I have to water my flowers today!"
He hasn't changed.
You don't say...
Eh, you can't win them all.
Speaking of, did you see today's game?
It was awesome, right?
What a team!
You're such a gentle young man.
Ninya?
But you know,
gentleness isn't always enough.
You need to be a little more assertive.
How can I?
Return to the forest, and speak to Burgalad.
He will give you the extra push you need.
But I can't understand him!
You'll need to use a decipher stone to speak with him.
A decipher stone? From where?!
Ninya, wait!