Hello there!
We're glad to see you!
Allow me to introduce you to my friend, Melkinso.
How can I help?
Schopello said I'd learn about hatching Laputa here.
Yes, a task that requires
the use of five special ores.
I need rocks for this?
The lapis lazuli,
the biome seed,
the high-grade synthester,
the flying stone,
and finally, the low-grade synthester.
Recently, we tried to collect all five ores,
and take them to the quiet laputa nest.
But before we could land,
Takatsung airships interfered!
The Takatsung forces want to use the ores
to create a megezo so powerful
it sucks up all the magic from us magicians of Iblard!
The ores fell out!
Oh no! The synthesters—
They triggered a rift in space-time!
Four ores landed safely in Iblard,
but one, the low-grade synthester,
slipped through space-time and landed in your world!
As for your plight,
those ores trigger a similar rift when hatching a laputa.
Do you get it? That rift should be able to send you home!
Actually, we were hoping you could help us find the ores.
With the Takatsung out there, we can't do it alone.
Do you know where the ores have fallen?
Ninya will know.
You should visit her shop in the next town over.
Is Ninya the woman I saw you two with?
Yes. Now, I'll lend you my airship.
It's old, but it's reliable.
I think its energy source is running low, though.
Thank you both.
I'll be off now!